{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Heater Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40369/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40369,"taskName":"Swimming Pool Heaters - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Swimming Pool Heaters","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Heater Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":186,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Pools sauna material heating replacement","textMessagingName":"Install Pool Heater","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms will install or replace any of the equipment that makes a swimming  pool work correctly.","rolloverShortDesc":"Filters, pumps, bubblers, heaters, chlorinators, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Swimming Pool Heaters.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pool Heater Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace a Pool Heater","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Swimming Pool Heaters Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool Heaters - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Heater Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-Heaters-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Heater Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Pools,sauna,material,heating,replacement,maintenance,costs,tub,hot,ground,inground,Swimming,Heaters,above,Equipment,semi","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":663,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40369/":{"taskOID":40369,"originalTaskOID":40369,"setID":663,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4909,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool needs heating? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3185,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4912,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of heater do you want to use? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4041,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4943,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Propane-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5873,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar heater","answerDisplayText":"Solar heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2835,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5023,"questionDisplayText":"Location of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is it an indoor or outdoor pool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4909,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool needs heating? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3185,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3185,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4912,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of heater do you want to use? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4041,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4943,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Propane-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5873,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar heater","answerDisplayText":"Solar heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2835,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4041,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4943,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane-gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Propane-gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2948,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5873,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar heater","answerDisplayText":"Solar heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2835,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5023,"questionDisplayText":"Location of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is it an indoor or outdoor pool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}